(Sheldon:)Yeah, maybe you better.
I took a pretty big sip.
(Howard:)Look, she's a grown woman.
(Howard:)And... and your dad's been
gone a long time.
(Howard:)Maybe this is none of your business.
(Sheldon:)I beg to differ.
(Sheldon:)I used to live in those genitals.
(Sheldon:)And if someone wants
to move into my old room,
(Sheldon:)I should at least get a vote.
(Raj:)Okay, murder suspects,
(Raj:)Leonard has found the time
machine the killer must've used.
(Raj:)You're all inside it, and we hurtle
through the very fabric of time.
I (SCI-FI LASER SOUNDS)
(Raj:)And welcome
to 20 years in the future.
Hey, you guys just time-traveled.
Stop looking so bored.
(Penny:)Well, my beer isn't flat
and my rack's not saggy.